{
  "1": {
    "1": { "front": "Rye Doubt These Dorm", "back": "Ride Out the Storm" },
    "2": {
      "front": "Ash Hold Hurt Hook Rye Yawn",
      "back": "A Shoulder To Cry On"
    },
    "3": { "front": "Aged Who Woe", "back": "H2O" },
    "4": { "front": "Aim Air Egg Gore Round", "back": "A Merry–Go–Round" },
    "5": { "front": "Air Hub Herb Hand", "back": "A Rubber Band" },
    "6": { "front": "Aid Us Sinner Owe Hoses", "back": "A Dozen Roses" },
    "7": { "front": "Canoe Key Pace He Grit", "back": "Can You Keep A Secret" },
    "8": { "front": "Check Hinge ill", "back": "Jack and Jill" },
    "9": { "front": "Aid Ride Hyper", "back": "A Dry Diaper" },
    "10": { "front": "Egg Hull Art Eve He", "back": "A Color TV" },
    "11": { "front": "Bills Pair Read Oh Boy", "back": "Pillsbury Dough Boy" },
    "12": { "front": "Abe Ax Tree Tally", "back": "A Back Street Alley" },
    "13": {
      "front": "Snot Mike Up Puffed He",
      "back": "It's Not My Cup of Tea"
    },
    "14": { "front": "Abe An An Appeal", "back": "A banana peal" },
    "15": {
      "front": "Comb Bee Forth Ease Dorm",
      "back": "Calm Before The Storm"
    }
  },
  "2": {
    "1": { "front": "Con Face Shores Hens", "back": "Conversations" },
    "2": {
      "front": "Ate Rip Toot His Kneel Hand",
      "back": "A Trip To Disneyland"
    },
    "3": { "front": "Abe Bless Sing", "back": "A Blessing" },
    "4": { "front": "Below They Whiz ill", "back": "Blow the Whistle" },
    "5": { "front": "Disc Possible Dye Purse", "back": "Disposable Diapers" },
    "6": { "front": "Adore Purr Eyes", "back": "A Door Prize" },
    "7": { "front": "Owl Frayed Hose Hoss", "back": "Alfredo Sauce" },
    "8": { "front": "Dawn Bed Tone Kit", "back": "Don't Bet On It" },
    "9": { "front": "Aid Hub Bladee Gent", "back": "A Double Agent" },
    "10": { "front": "Aid Are Crank Loud", "back": "A Dark Rain Cloud" },
    "11": { "front": "Portal Ann Dory Gun", "back": "Portland" },
    "12": { "front": "Easel Aid Ease Man", "back": "He's A Ladies Man" },
    "13": { "front": "Hiney Dairy Seat", "back": "I Need a Receipt" },
    "14": { "front": "Egg Know Rinses Bless", "back": "Ignorance is Bliss" },
    "15": { "front": "Aid Arrive Her Slice Sins", "back": "A Drivers License" }
  },
  "3": {
    "1": { "front": "Ace Heal Ink Van", "back": "A Ceiling Fan" },
    "2": {
      "front": "Age High Knees West Want",
      "back": "A Chinese Restaurant"
    },
    "3": { "front": "Crawl Shore Fiend Curse", "back": "Cross Your Fingers" },
    "4": { "front": "Ache Up Puck Off He", "back": "A Cup of Coffee" },
    "5": { "front": "Disguise They'll Him Hit", "back": "The Skies the Limit" },
    "6": { "front": "Fooled Forth Halt", "back": "Food For Thought" },
    "7": { "front": "Arrest Hairy Ahh", "back": "A Rest Area" },
    "8": {
      "front": "Dawn Ways Chore Moan Knit",
      "back": "Don't Waste Your Time On It"
    },
    "9": {
      "front": "Any Lack Tricked Bull Hank Hit",
      "back": "An Electric Blanket"
    },
    "10": { "front": "Abe Autumn Lisp Hit", "back": "A Bottomless Pit" },
    "11": { "front": "A Lick Cue All Ought", "back": "I Like You Alot" },
    "12": { "front": "Bull Line Days Sub Hat", "back": "Blind As A Bat" },
    "13": { "front": "Cause Mid Ticks Urge Jury", "back": "Cosmetic Surgery" },
    "14": { "front": "Dawn Bees Hose Hilly", "back": "Don't Be So Silly" },
    "15": { "front": "Cough He Anchor Ream", "back": "Coffee and Cream" }
  },
  "4": {
    "1": { "front": "Calm Hunger Hound", "back": "Common Ground" },
    "2": { "front": "Call Fibber Rake", "back": "Coffee Break" },
    "3": {
      "front": "Dune Hot Feed Than Hymn Hulls",
      "back": "Do Not Feed the Animals"
    },
    "4": { "front": "Dowel List Excess", "back": "Dallas" },
    "5": { "front": "Ask Rude Arrive Her", "back": "A Screw Driver" },
    "6": { "front": "Crown Dogged Hay", "back": "Ground Hog Day" },
    "7": { "front": "Ace Lie Soap Eye", "back": "A Slice of Pie" },
    "8": { "front": "Offend Herb End Her", "back": "A Fender Bender" },
    "9": { "front": "Ape Hack Awful Eyes", "back": "A Pack Of Lies" },
    "10": {
      "front": "Beyond Nest Wit Chores Elf",
      "back": "Be Honest With Yourself"
    },
    "11": {
      "front": "Ache Hood Sin Sew Fume Her",
      "back": "A Good Sense of Humor"
    },
    "12": {
      "front": "Wore Have Ink Abe Abe He",
      "back": "We're Having a Baby"
    },
    "13": { "front": "Creased My Sieve", "back": "Christmas Eve" },
    "14": { "front": "Ale Hot Treat Hick Hit", "back": "A Lottery Ticket" },
    "15": { "front": "Backed Ooze Queer Won", "back": "Back to Square One" }
  },
  "5": {
    "1": { "front": "Knots Hole Dens Tores", "back": "Not Sold in Stores" },
    "2": { "front": "Dried Hog Feud", "back": "Dry Dog Food" },
    "3": { "front": "Ball Stint Heap Hearty", "back": "Boston Tea Party" },
    "4": {
      "front": "Bat Tree Snot Ink Looted",
      "back": "Batteries Not Included"
    },
    "5": { "front": "Aid Hymn Oak Rat", "back": "A Democrat" },
    "6": { "front": "Dawn Jury Member", "back": "Don't You Remember" },
    "7": { "front": "Calm Tooth Hen Cove Fit", "back": "Come To Think Of It" },
    "8": {
      "front": "Arrow Loved oil It Issue",
      "back": "A Roll of Toilet Tissue"
    },
    "9": { "front": "Use Yell Knots Deal", "back": "You Shall Not Steal" },
    "10": { "front": "Better Hoses", "back": "Bed of Roses" },
    "11": {
      "front": "Caress Tougher Clump Us",
      "back": "Christopher Columbus"
    },
    "12": { "front": "Beam Hive Howl Lint I'm", "back": "Be My Valentine" },
    "13": { "front": "Aid Inn Hearse Owl Add", "back": "A Dinner Salad" },
    "14": { "front": "Chess Tame Home Hint", "back": "Just a Moment" },
    "15": { "front": "Delights Havens Dime", "back": "Daylight Savings Time" }
  },
  "6": {
    "1": { "front": "Bee Way Rough Thud Hog", "back": "Beware of the Dog" },
    "2": {
      "front": "Jostle Hit Tub Hit Mower",
      "back": "Just A Little Bit More"
    },
    "3": { "front": "Burr Sofa Faith Her", "back": "Birds of a Feather" },
    "4": { "front": "By Chore Dung", "back": "Bite Your Toung" },
    "5": { "front": "Check Cove Fault Raids", "back": "Jack of All Trades" },
    "6": { "front": "Cussed Hum Aid", "back": "Custom Made" },
    "7": { "front": "Acre Hill Uh", "back": "A Gorilla" },
    "8": { "front": "Aim Who Very View", "back": "A Movie Review" },
    "9": { "front": "Bare Love Monk Ease", "back": "A Barrel of Monkies" },
    "10": {
      "front": "Ace Height Force or Rise",
      "back": "A Sight For Sore Eyes"
    },
    "11": { "front": "Ale Hawk Cab Hen", "back": "A Log Cabin" },
    "12": { "front": "Apart Hinder", "back": "A Bar Tender" },
    "13": { "front": "Al of Try Ankle", "back": "A Love Triangle" },
    "14": { "front": "Acre Halls Tub Hoard", "back": "Across the Board" },
    "15": { "front": "Aid Hay Huff Ache Asian", "back": "A Day of Vacation" }
  },
  "7": {
    "1": {
      "front": "Dawn Tall Quit Chore Mile Full",
      "back": "Don't Talk With Your Mouth Full"
    },
    "2": { "front": "Echoed Uh Fifth Hicks", "back": "A Code of Ethics" },
    "3": { "front": "Know Won Candy High Yet", "back": "No One Can Deny It" },
    "4": { "front": "May Pole Sir Up", "back": "Maple Syrup" },
    "5": { "front": "Ace Nose Dorm", "back": "A Snow Storm" },
    "6": { "front": "Ear Wig Hoe Hug Hen", "back": "Here We Go Again" },
    "7": { "front": "Aim Adder Rough Open Yen", "back": "A Matter of Opinion" },
    "8": { "front": "Ace Pea Ding Tea Kit", "back": "A Speeding Ticket" },
    "9": {
      "front": "Bigger Scant Beach Hoosiers",
      "back": "Beggars Can't Be Choosers"
    },
    "10": {
      "front": "Ewe Arm Eye Ever Wreath In",
      "back": "You Are My Everything"
    },
    "11": { "front": "Ace Leap Lesson Height", "back": "A Sleepless Night" },
    "12": { "front": "Age Are Coke Real", "back": "A Charcoal Grill" },
    "13": {
      "front": "Ape Arrows Uncle As His",
      "back": "A Pair of Sunglasses"
    },
    "14": {
      "front": "Aisle Beer Height They Hair",
      "back": "I'll Be Right There"
    },
    "15": { "front": "Check Hole Ant Turn", "back": "Jack–O–Lantern" }
  },
  "8": {
    "1": { "front": "Annex Tin Chunk Hoard", "back": "An Extension Cord" },
    "2": { "front": "Dawn Buried Hick Yule Us", "back": "Don't Be Ridiculous" },
    "3": { "front": "Dare Snow Window Wit", "back": "There's No End To It" },
    "4": { "front": "Ache Off Cores", "back": "A Golf Course" },
    "5": { "front": "Dad Donor Eyeful", "back": "Dead On Arrival" },
    "6": {
      "front": "Aim Honey Bag Care Runt He",
      "back": "A Money Back Guarantee"
    },
    "7": { "front": "Debt Snot Must Aisle", "back": "That's Not My Style" },
    "8": { "front": "Diamond Dime Hun Hen", "back": "Time and Time Again" },
    "9": { "front": "Aim Hiker Owes Cope", "back": "A Microscope" },
    "10": { "front": "Beast ill My Art", "back": "Be Still My Heart" },
    "11": { "front": "Each Oar Hard Tout", "back": "Eat Your Heart Out" },
    "12": { "front": "Hits Owe Wad", "back": "It's So Odd" },
    "13": { "front": "Ace Heck Hunch Ants", "back": "A Second Chance" },
    "14": {
      "front": "Age Rob Pin Tub Huck Kit",
      "back": "A Drop in the Bucket"
    },
    "15": { "front": "Aim Other Ranch Howled", "back": "A Mother and Child" }
  }
}
